question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The movie &quot;The Nightmare before Christmas&quot; was all done with physical objects.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Leonardo DiCaprio won an Oscar for Best Actor in 2004&#039;s &quot;The Aviator&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The film &quot;2001: A Space Odyssey&quot; was released on December 31st, 2000.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Matt Damon played an astronaut stranded on an extraterrestrial planet in both of the movies Interstellar and The Martian.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The 2010 film &quot;The Social Network&quot; is a biographical drama film about MySpace founder Tom Anderson.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the original script of &quot;The Matrix&quot;, the machines used humans as additional computing power instead of batteries.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Alfred Hitchcock&#039;s film &#039;Psycho&#039; it is said he used chocolate syrup to simulate the blood in the famous shower scene from ",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, Alec Guinness provided the voice for Darth Vader.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Brandon Routh plays the titular character in the movie &quot;John Wick&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "&quot;Foodfight!&quot; earned less than $80,000 at box office.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
